so now your code is executing but it
所以现在您的代码正在执行，但是
doesn't have all the frames all the
没有所有的框架
colors on the stack so yields gonna
堆栈上的颜色会产生
return to to the C method and he's gonna
回到C方法，他将
run and let's say C now wants to return
运行，假设C现在想返回
who is C C's callers C's caller is B but
C的呼叫者是谁C的呼叫者是B但
it's not in a socket but when C returns
它不在套接字中，但是当C返回时
is going to hit that return barrier and
将会达到回报壁垒，
that return barrier is gonna call saw
那个返回障碍会叫锯
again and that's gonna copy the next
再次，这将复制下一个
frame and does the whole thing with oops
框架并完成整个操作
again it's going to turn to B it's gonna
再次将变成B
install the return barrier again but
再次安装回流挡板，但是
then it's possible that B doesn't want
那么B可能不想要
to return to a like said it could be a
回到一个说可能是一个
hundred methods deep and you're only
一百种方法，而你只是
looping at the topmost few frames so B
在最上面的几帧循环播放，因此B
is going to call let's say D and D is
会打电话给我们，假设D和D是
going to yield so we only have those
要屈服，所以我们只有那些
those frames to copy so the cost of the
这些框架要复制，因此
operation now is linear and the amount
现在的操作是线性的，并且数量
of stack you've used in the last time
您上次使用的堆栈数量
you've continued so it's basically the
您已经继续，所以基本上
overhead is is constant and the question
开销是恒定的，这个问题
is whether or not we can make it fast
是我们是否可以使其快速发展
enough so actually this whole copying
足够，所以实际上整个复制
thing is very fast
事情很快
it's hardly you know it's it's nothing
你几乎不知道那是什么
to worry about the cost we've hit right
担心我们付出的代价是正确的
now is the operations of actually
现在实际上是
walking the frames and and that is
走帧，那就是
something that we're trying to make
我们正在努力做的事情
faster but the more interesting bit is
更快，但更有趣的是
extracting loops finding the finding the
提取循环查找结果
references and the stack and extracting
引用和堆栈并提取
them and that is something that regard
他们，这是有关的东西
here from the Sock'em office is going to
来自Sock'em办公室的
try to make faster maybe by generating
尝试通过产生更快的速度
some native code instead of generating
一些本地代码而不是生成
machine code instead of doing in a seats
机器代码而不是坐在座位上
the fallback is if we cannot get it to
退路是如果我们无法做到这一点
be fast enough is to change the compiler
足够快是要更改编译器
and the way the compilers emit code but
以及编译器发出代码的方式
that is something that can be a lot of
那可能是很多
work and we're trying to get it to work
工作，我们正在努力使它工作
for first and then to make it fast
首先，然后使其快速
and right now I think we think that
现在我想我们认为
we can get this to be as as fast as we
我们可以使它和我们一样快
need this is also a slide to show you
需要这张幻灯片给你看
last series said that the things that
最后一个系列说的东西
are going to be need to be retrofitted
将需要进行改造
or the i/o so when you do any i/o
或I / O，所以当您执行任何I / O时
operation it's going to need to know not
操作将需要不知道
to call the blocking i/o operations all
调用所有阻塞的I / O操作
the job YouTube concurrence so if you
YouTube同意这份工作，如果您
lock and you're inside a fiber it has to
锁定，并且您必须处于光纤内部
block the fiber not the underlying
阻止纤维而不是底层
kernel thread and I also mentioned I
内核线程，我也提到了我
think some people asked about this too I
我想也有人问过这个
also mentioned that if you run threads
还提到如果您运行线程
in the operating system most of the time
大多数时候在操作系统中
the way the the operating system is
操作系统的方式
going to D schedule your thread and run
去D安排线程并运行
another thread in the same CPU when you
当您在同一CPU中的另一个线程
actually block an i/o that is a normal
实际上阻​​止了一个正常的I / O
case but occasionally you have a thread
情况下，但偶尔你有一个线程
that's just doing a lot of computation
那只是做大量的计算
for a very long time and after a certain
在很长一段时间内
while the operating system is going to
当操作系统将要
preempt it and say run for long enough
抢占它并说运行了足够长的时间
let someone else run and seeing some I
让别人跑去看我
think some people asked whether we could
认为有人问我们是否可以
do it with fibers and they said maybe
用纤维做，他们说也许
and if we do we can rely on the
如果我们这样做，我们可以依靠
safepoint mechanism and actually we
安全点机制，实际上我们
ended up doing just that we are not
最终只是说我们不是
entirely certain whether or not we're
完全确定我们是否
actually gonna need it and the reason is
实际上会需要它，原因是
this if you have something like eight
如果你有八个
cores and say 20 threads and some of the
核心，并说20个线程和一些
do IO and some of them do a lot of CP a
做IO，其中一些做很多CP
lot of CPU operations it is certainly
大量的CPU操作肯定是
possible that some of them will need to
其中一些人可能需要
be preempted because they take up too
被抢占，因为他们也占用
much CPU but if you have a million of
很多CPU，但是如果您有一百万
those threads and say a thousand of them
这些线程，说一千
use so much CPU that you need to
使用太多的CPU，您需要
forcefully preempt them then you're
强行抢占他们，那么你就是
under provisioned I mean there's not
供应不足，我的意思是没有
much any kind of scheduling can help you
任何类型的调度都可以帮助您
so it's not like if you have so many
所以这不像你有那么多
threads that all of them need so much
他们都非常需要的线程
CPU that preemption is what you need
需要抢占的CPU
then you screwed either way
然后你用任何一种方式拧
but the reason we decided to add this
但是我们决定添加这个的原因
anyways is that some people may what
无论如何，有些人可能会
they may want to do is not to try to
他们可能想做的是不要尝试
solve the problem by scheduling fibers
通过安排光纤解决问题
cleverly but if they see a fiber that
聪明地但是如果他们看到纤维
takes up too much CPU they're gonna say
他们会说占用过多的CPU
that fiber is misbehaving they want to
光纤行为异常，他们想
take it off and maybe run it you know an
脱掉它，也许运行它，你知道
hour later when when there is more room
一小时后，当有更多房间时
in the machine so this is what we have
在机器上，这就是我们所拥有的
now I showed you we have in the part in
现在我告诉你我们参与了
the in the prototype we have nessa
在原型中，我们有nessa
continuations I'll show what snack
继续，我会告诉你什么零食
walking is stuff we don't have now
走路是我们现在没有的东西
continuations are very low-level
延续性很低
mechanism some in some languages people
机制有些语言的人
use continuations directly so they have
直接使用延续，所以他们有
like higher level abstraction that
像更高层次的抽象
allows you to pass values from the run
允许您从运行中传递值
point to the yield point so the next
指向屈服点，所以下一个
time you continue the continuation you
当你继续延续时
can pass it in arguments and that's the
可以在参数中传递它，这就是
arguments going to be returned from
将要从中返回的参数
yield it's very easy to implement in
产生它很容易实现
Java on top of the continuations we have
Java是我们拥有的延续
just we haven't done it yet we want to
只是我们还没有做到
be able to clone continuations so
能够克隆延续
continuation remembers its own remembers
延续记得自己的回忆
its current States and next time you run
当前状态和下次运行
it it can so it remembers its current
它可以记住它的当前状态
state it's puts it off to the sides the
说明它放到一边
next time you run it it mutates the
下次您运行它时，
state right but maybe in some cases you
声明正确，但在某些情况下您
want to go back in time and run the same
想回到过去并运行相同的
computation again from the same point so
从同一点再次计算
what you can do is you just clone it so
你可以做的就是克隆它
if you clone the continuation you can
如果克隆延续，则可以
continue it multiple times serialization
连续多次序列化
is another very interesting thing we
是我们另一个非常有趣的事情
haven't started working on that either
都还没有开始工作
so you may want to block the
所以您可能想阻止
continuation to do the continuation and
继续做延续
maybe continue in a different machine or
也许在另一台机器上继续
serialize it to disk and continue it a
序列化到磁盘，然后继续
month from now and one serious
从现在开始一个月，一个严重的
limitation we have now is I mentioned
我现在提到的限制是
that if you have an eight
如果你有一个八
frame on the stack the continuation is
框架在堆栈上的延续是
pinned it cannot yield that is probably
固定它不能产生可能是
going to stay forever but a current
将永远停留，但潮流
limitation we have is that you're also
我们的限制是你也是
pinned if the continuation is currently
固定，如果当前是延续
holding a native monitor so if you are
抱着一个本机监视器，所以如果你是
currently inside a synchronized method
当前在同步方法中
or a synchronized block and you try to
或同步块，您尝试
yield while you are inside the
当你在里面的时候屈服
synchronized block you will be pinned as
同步块，您将被固定为
well job ito concurrent locks work but
并发锁工作很好，但是
native monitors will pin you and that is
本机监视器将固定您，那就是
a limitation that we'll probably want to
我们可能想要的限制
get rid of later so this is more or less
摆脱以后，所以或多或少
the API the API we have now so I showed
API我们现在拥有的API
you the the first few methods at the
您的前几种方法
beginning we have some stuff to to let
开始，我们有一些东西要让
you walk the stack while the
你走栈时
continuation is unmounted and this is
连续被卸载，这是
the force preemption thing you can try
可以尝试的强制抢先
to ask a continuation that's running in
询问正在运行的延续
a different thread please yield yourself
不同的线程请让自己
and the way that works is inside hotspot
而工作方式是在热点内
we have a thread local handshake it
我们有一个线程本地握手
basically takes a small closure and asks
基本上需要一个小封闭，然后问
the VM to run that closure at the next
VM在下一次运行该关闭
safe point and if we do that at the next
安全点，如果我们下次再这样做
safe points it would call yield of
安全点，将其称为
course it may not succeed because maybe
当然它可能不会成功，因为也许
you're pinned so you may need to try a
您已固定，因此您可能需要尝试
few times okay so far about
到目前为止还好几次
continuations any questions and then
继续任何问题，然后
that is the main so only continuations
那是主要的，所以只有延续
are implemented in the VM that is the
在VM中实现
main portion and now I'll show how
主要部分，现在我将展示如何
fibers are implement stop that but any
纤维是工具停止，但任何
questions so far okay
到目前为止的问题还可以
once you have continuations you can
一旦有了延续，就可以
build lightweight threads on top of them
在它们之上构建轻量级线程
so what are threads threads require a
那么什么是线程线程需要一个
continuation which is some piece of code
延续，这是一段代码
that can stop and be resumed at a later
可以停止并在以后恢复
point in time and a scheduler which is
时间点和一个调度程序是
something that takes many of these
需要很多这样的东西
continuations and decides when to run
继续并决定何时运行
each of them so a thread can say now I'm
他们每个人都这样一个线程可以说我
ready to run or now I want to block so
准备运行或现在我要阻止
please take me off the cpu and it can
请让我离开CPU，它可以
get a signal now I'm ready to run so it
现在收到信号，我已经准备好运行了
has to tell the scheduler I'm ready to
必须告诉调度程序我已经准备好
run and when the scheduler finds the
运行，当调度程序找到
right time it assigns it to a CPU so
在正确的时间将其分配给CPU，因此
basically this is the same way it works
基本上这是相同的方式
in the kernel any kind of thread is
在内核中，任何类型的线程都是
really a thread has a continuation and
实际上，线程具有延续性，
it has a scheduler so when we do
它有一个调度程序，所以当我们这样做
lightweight threads and runtime fibers
轻量级线程和运行时光纤
we do the same way continuations are
我们以相同的方式继续
provided to us by the VM and the
虚拟机和
scheduler we use any Java executor by
调度程序，我们使用任何Java执行程序
default we're using fork/join pool
默认我们使用fork / join池
because it's a great fit for this kind
因为它非常适合这种情况
of workload so every fiber has a
工作量，因此每根光纤都有一个
continuation in just scheduler how are
只是调度程序中的延续
the two related so if you know Java chip
两者相关，所以如果您知道Java芯片
concurrent I expect most of you do and
并发，我希望你们大多数人都这样做，
you try to obtain a lock or there were a
您尝试获取锁，或者有一个
phaser or all the oldie Java trickle
移相器或所有旧版Java le流
current classes and for some reason the
当前的课程，由于某种原因
lock is not available it's held by
锁不可用，由它持有
someone else and now you need to block
别人，现在你需要阻止
and it is that blocking operation that
就是阻塞操作
currently blocks the current kernel
当前阻止当前内核
thread and we want it so that if you're
线程，我们想要它，以便如果您
in a fiber it would only block the fiber
在光纤中只会阻塞光纤
so all of the code in Java till
所以所有的Java代码直到
concurrent that blocks the kernel thread
阻塞内核线程的并发
today goes through this method Java
今天通过这种方法Java
concurrent locks lock support Park
并发锁锁支持园区
that's the method so this is a not too
那是方法，所以这不是太
different from the code we have in the
与我们的代码不同
prototype today just took up a few bits
今天的原型只占了一些位
about you know bookkeeping there's a
关于你知道簿记有一个
call of the blocker we keep track of who
封锁者的电话，我们跟踪谁
wanted to block you but basically this
想阻止你，但基本上
is it we ask for whether we first of all
我们首先要问我们是否
we ask whether we're running in ordinary
我们问我们是否在平凡中跑步
thread
线
or we have or we're inside a fiber so we
或者我们有或者我们在纤维内部，所以我们
call that concept a strand so a strand
称这个概念为一股股线
is either kernel thread or lightwei
是内核线程还是lightwei
thread over fiber I talked about it a
光纤上的线我谈到了
bit last year since then I said them
去年以来，我说他们
maybe we'll add like a super type for
也许我们会为它添加一个超级类型
threads and fibers called strands we we
线和纤维称为股线我们
had that in an earlier prototype we took
在我们早期的原型中
it out because there was very little to
出来，因为几乎没有
do in uh in strands so right now it's
在一堆里做，所以现在
basically just an object but but I'll
基本上只是一个对象，但我会
get to that to the design a bit so if it
进行一些设计，如果它
is a thread we call unsafe lock Park and
是我们称为不安全锁Park的线程
that asks the kernel to suspend the
要求内核挂起
current thread but if it is a fiber this
当前线程，但如果是光纤，则
just yields the fibers continuation so
只是产生纤维的延续，所以
this is this is what Park would do say
这就是朴会说的
if you can't get the lock it will just
如果您无法获得锁，它将只是
get translated to a continuation yield
被翻译成连续产量
on the fibers on the fibers continuation
在纤维上的纤维延续
and if you're already holding the lock
如果您已经持有锁
and now you want to release it what you
现在您想释放它
do there is a list of there's a queue of
是否有一个队列列表
threads are waiting and you take the
线程正在等待，你把
first one and you wake them up and this
第一个，你叫醒他们，这个
is done in Java took current always
用Java完成总是需要电流
through this method on Park and if it is
通过这种方法在公园，如果是
a thread it's gonna go to unsafe and ask
一个线程，它将去不安全并询问
the kernel to do that for you but if it
内核为您做到这一点，但如果它
is a fiber it's going to take the fiber
是一种纤维，它将带走纤维
scheduler and it's just going to submit
调度程序，它只是要提交
the fibers continuation so the scheduler
光纤连续，因此调度程序
is going to get submitted a task and
将要提交任务，
when the scheduler gets around to it
当调度程序处理它时
it's going to run that task and it's
它要运行该任务，并且
going to call the run method on the task
要在任务上调用run方法
but for continuation run continues from
但为了继续运行，从
the yield point so this gives you
屈服点，所以这给你
exactly the same behavior is blocking
完全相同的行为正在阻止
you're going to continue from the last
你将从上一个继续
point from the point where you blocked
从您阻止的点开始
and this is how fibers and continuations
这就是纤维和延续
relate so a fiber as a scheduler and a
因此，将光纤作为调度程序和
continuation so
如此延续
right now in fibers have a very thin and
现在的纤维非常细
minimal API and it also changes like
最小的API，它也会像
every week explain why in a bit but if
每周解释一下为什么，但是如果
you want to create a new fiber this is
您想创建一个新的光纤
how you do it
你怎么做
currently fibers can return results
目前纤维可以返回结果
unlike threads so this is how you join a
不像线程，所以这就是你加入一个
fiber and you get the results all the
纤维，您将获得所有结果
code in libraries javi took concurrence
javi库中的代码并发
all of the i/o has been retrofitted to
所有的I / O都进行了改装
work with fibers one thing you got to
使用纤维一件事
say they're one of the nio was
说他们是尼尼奥人之一
retrofitted to work with fibers a while
改装后可与光纤配合使用一段时间
ago but something happened just in the
以前，但是在
last few weeks is that all of the old
最近几周是所有旧的
i/o the old network hanging api the old
I / O旧网络挂api旧
sockets API has been retrofitted as well
套接字API也进行了改进
in the way that's done now is actually
以现在完成的方式实际上是
pretty exciting for us at least as
至少对我们来说很令人兴奋
maintainer of the VM is that all viola
VM的维护者是所有中提琴
old i/o is 20 year old code that's
I / O是20年的旧代码
written in C and what Allen has done he
用C语言写的，艾伦做了什么
has really implemented the old i/o on
确实实现了旧的I / O
top of nao so old i/o is now implemented
nao的顶部，因此现在已实现了旧的I / O
entirely in java and he got it to pass
完全用Java，他成功了
all the tests there would still be maybe
所有的测试也许仍然存在
some corner cases because it's very old
一些极端的情况，因为它很旧
code so we expect that for maybe for a
代码，所以我们期望
version or two people would have the
版本或两个人将有
option of either using the old C code or
使用旧C代码或
the new implementation of old i/o in
旧I / O的新实现
Java but eventually that C code is going
Java，但最终C代码正在发展
to go away it's gonna be just Java it is
走开，它将只是Java
also easy to mix fibers with futures one
也容易将纤维与期货
thing here just so you see the the kind
事情在这里，只是让您看到那种
of difficulties that arise and and when
出现的困难以及何时
you try to put something new like this
你尝试像这样放一些新东西
into the old JDK you can turn a fiber
到旧的JDK中，您可以将光纤
into a future but a fiber does not
进入未来，但光纤不会
implement future why is that because
实施未来的原因是因为
future has some very interesting
未来有一些很有趣
semantics defined in the specification
规范中定义的语义
for example if you have a future and you
例如，如果你有未来，而你
call cancel that cancellation is atomic
取消呼叫是原子的
the next time if you ask the future if
下次如果你问未来
you're done
你完成了
even if it hasn't completed executing
即使尚未完成执行
yet it will say yes
但它会说是
that's the API for futures for fibers if
这是纤维期货的API，如果
you want to ask whether you're done we
你想问你是否完成了
really want to know if you're terminated
真的想知道你是否被解雇了
so even though the methods are the same
所以即使方法是一样的
the semantics are different so instead
语义是不同的，所以
of having fiber implements futures you
纤维实现期货的方法
can we can ask to convert them to a
我们可以要求将它们转换为
future we have some support in the
未来我们会在
debugger already so you can step through
调试器已经存在，因此您可以逐步完成
fibers you can get a list see a bit of
纤维，你可以得到一个列表，看到一点
see a list of the fibers but this is
看到纤维的清单，但这是
another problem again so you got to
另一个问题，所以你必须
think about debugging and unlike threads
考虑调试和与线程不同
you can have maybe a couple of thousands
你可能有几千
of them here you can have millions so
他们这里可以有数百万
obviously just sending the list of
显然只是发送清单
fibers to the to the debugger is going
到调试器的光纤正在运行
to take a while so you have to think how
花一点时间，所以你必须考虑如何
to do that so maybe just certain fibers
做到这一点，所以也许只是某些纤维
at you mark maybe just the fibers that
在您身上标记的可能只是
you set a breakpoint on there is some
您在其中设置了一个断点
stuff there when it comes to management
管理方面的东西
and JFR we haven't even started that yet
和JFR，我们还没有开始
I'm ashamed I have almost nothing okay
我很as愧，我几乎没事了
so I'm gonna skip that alright so in
所以我要跳过那个
terms of what we've accomplished of
我们所完成的工作的条件
making them lightweight a thread has in
使它们轻巧
Java has two kilobytes of metadata and
Java有2 KB的元数据，
by default one megabyte of stack for
默认情况下，一兆字节的堆栈用于
fibers it's two hundred three hundred
纤维是两百三百
bytes of metadata it's going to go down
元数据字节将下降
and the stack grows and shrink as you go
栈随着您的成长而增长和缩小
because it's in the heap and we allocate
因为它在堆里，我们分配
it as needed can be a few bytes it can
根据需要可以是几个字节
be a few kilobytes me a few megabytes
几千字节，我几兆字节
the task switching calls for threads is
切换线程的任务是
between like one and ten microseconds it
大约一到十微秒
can be even more we're still working on
可能还会更多，我们仍在努力
performance so we don't know what the
性能，所以我们不知道
SAS wishing calls for fibers is but it's
SAS希望有光纤需求，但这是
gonna be substantially less so less than
会大大小于
five minutes okay
五分钟好
so so far my hope was that you know
到目前为止，我的希望是你知道
fibers are just implementation of
光纤只是实现
threads let's just take the thread API
线程让我们仅采用线程API
we have maybe add a new constructor that
我们也许添加了一个新的构造函数
was my dream just I don't like coming up
是我的梦想，只是我不喜欢上来
with new api's so I thought
用新的api，所以我想
[Music]
[音乐]
we already have an API for threading if
我们已经有一个线程的API，如果
we could just get another constructor
我们可以得到另一个构造函数
for thread that maybe takes a scheduler
对于可能需要调度程序的线程
parameter and then you get a fiber and
参数，然后得到光纤
that's it that would be do a lot of work
就是要做很多工作
in the VM some working libraries but in
在VM中一些工作库，但在
terms of API design we'll use whatever
API设计条款，我们将使用任何
we have but then we talk to the
我们有，但随后我们与
architects mark John and Brian and they
建筑师纪念约翰和布莱恩，他们
said listen you're working with
说听你在和谁一起工作
concurrency and after 20 years there's a
并发，20年后
good opportunity to make some changes so
进行一些更改的好机会
maybe start the beginning and so this is
也许从头开始，所以这是
I think the difference between Java and
我认为Java和
maybe other languages other languages
也许其他语言其他语言
want to get many users and they try to
想要获得许多用户，他们尝试
to get the attractive features in as
获得吸引人的功能
quickly as possible for us we know we've
对我们来说，尽快知道我们已经
been around for a long time and this
已经存在很长时间了
point we're certain we're gonna be
点，我们确定我们会成为
around for a long time yet so we need to
周围很长一段时间，所以我们需要
when we do something we try to think
当我们做某事时，我们试图思考
whether that's gonna be the right thing
那是否正确
for the next 20 years so you say ok so
接下来的20年，所以你说好
you're touching the concepts of threads
您触及线程的概念
maybe try start with nothing and see
也许尝试从零开始，看看
what he actually needs so instead of
他实际需要的是
using a thread API certain something
使用线程API的某些东西
that has nothing there and rethink
那里什么都没有，重新思考
threads so I thought it would probably
线程，所以我认为这可能
end up with the same thing so I didn't
以同样的事情结束，所以我没有
know really what's gonna be the result
真的知道会有什么结果
but shortly afterwards I ran into a blog
但是不久之后，我遇到了一个博客
post was actually two blog posts these
帖子实际上是两个博客帖子
one these ones by a Nathaniel J Smith
其中一个是纳撒尼尔·J·史密斯（Nathaniel J Smith）
writes live worship Python about
写关于Python的现场崇拜
something called a structured
所谓的结构化
concurrency he actually didn't come up
并发他实际上并没有出现
with the idea the idea yes he is
这个主意是他是
attributed to Martin sauce trick and
归因于马丁酱招和
structure when I read at least it was
当我至少阅读它时的结构是
one of these rare occasions when you
这些罕见的情况之一，当您
read a technical blog post and you say
阅读技术博客文章，您说
yeah obviously that that is the right
是的，显然那是正确的
way to do it it hasn't happened to me
做到这一点，这从来没有发生在我身上
many times during my career but this was
在我的职业生涯中很多次，但这是
one of them and we passed around and
其中之一，我们过去了，
pretty much everyone liked it so the
几乎每个人都喜欢它，所以
idea of structured concurrency is that
结构化并发的思想是
instead of taking threads and just
而不是采取线程而已
starting them and letting them run and
启动它们并让它们运行
complete whenever they want we manage
只要他们想要我们完成，
their life time more closely so we have
他们的生活时间更紧密，所以我们有
this thing that is currently called
目前被称为
fiber scope we already
光纤范围我们已经
have continuation scope but we have
有延续范围，但我们有
another kind of scope so the names will
另一种范围，因此名称将
probably change so you have a scope and
可能会改变，所以您有一个范围，
to try with resources block and the
尝试使用资源块和
fibers that you schedule inside that
您在其中安排的纤维
block you cannot exit the block until
封锁，直到您不能离开封锁
they are terminated so when you try to
它们被终止，所以当您尝试
so when you exit this block its going to
因此，当您退出此街区时，
call the close method on whatever this
不管什么都调用close方法
returns it's going to block until luck
返回它将一​​直阻塞直到运气好
when they say block not necessarily
当他们说不一定封锁
Colonel the kernel thread right so V
上校内核线程，所以V
block we can block fibers but it's going
阻止，我们可以阻止纤维，但是
to block until all the fibers in there
阻塞直到所有的纤维在那里
have terminated so we know that anything
已经终止了，所以我们知道
and even if they schedule other fibers
即使他们安排其他纤维
everything the entire tree of fibers is
整个纤维树都是
going to terminate when we exit we can
当我们退出时将终止
esos scopes and yes and you can cancel
esos范围，是的，您可以取消
the entire scope and if they are
整个范围，如果它们是
currently doing an eye operation that
目前正在做眼科手术
i/o operation is going to return and
I / O操作将返回，
signal somehow that it's been canceled
以某种方式表明它已被取消
this can do so you can do some clever
这样可以做到，你可以做一些聪明的事
things with it for example if you want
例如，如果需要的话
to run multiple things in parallel and
并行运行多件事
only wait for the first one so you start
只等第一个就开始
a fiber for each of the tasks and then
每个任务的光纤，然后
if we just ended here it would wait for
如果我们只是在这里结束，它将等待
all of them to terminate but instead
他们全部终止，但相反
they they get they all get put in a
他们得到他们都被放在一个
queue ordered by the termination order
终止顺序排序的队列
you wait until the first one terminates
你等到第一个终止
and then you cancel all the others the
然后您取消所有其他
you can also put a deadline on them so
你也可以给他们一个截止日期
if none of them terminates then all them
如果它们都没有终止，那么全部
won't get cancelled and the last thing
不会被取消，最后一件事
on top in the last minutes is thread
在最后几分钟，最重要的是线程
locals we want to replace them too
我们也想取代他们的当地人
because they're also kind of
因为它们也是
fire-and-forget you set a value and
一劳永逸地设置一个值，然后
maybe remember to reset it maybe not so
也许记得重置它，也许不是
we're trying to do something that's
我们正在尝试做的是
maybe more like
也许更像
dynamic variables and scheme where these
动态变量和方案，其中
thread load new thread locals called
线程加载称为
scoff locals have a scope and you've set
嘲笑当地人有范围，您已经设定
the value inside that scope is going to
该范围内的值将
be that value not necessarily it can be
是那个价值，不一定是
deep in the staff right so it's it works
在员工深处对，就是这样
like three locals you can access them
像三个当地人一样，您可以访问它们
anywhere but once you exit the scope
任何地方，但一旦退出示波器
they get reset to their old value and
他们重置为原来的值，
because we have fibers we also control
因为我们有纤维，我们也控制
the lifetime if you start new fibers
如果您开始使用新纤维，则使用寿命
here maybe they'll also they will also
在这里，也许他们也会
inherit this value but these are just
继承这个值，但是这些仅仅是
early ideas we actually we don't have
我们实际上没有的早期想法
this in the prototype yet and that is
这在原型中呢，那是
all I have to say sorry
我只想说对不起
any questions for Ron I'll start with
关于罗恩的任何问题，我将从
one actually tell me about your most
实际上告诉我你的最
interesting and impressive benchmarking
有趣而令人印象深刻的基准测试
results so far if you have any
到目前为止的结果，如果有的话